<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rhino.Render.ChangeQueue on Test API Site</title>
    <link>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rhino.Render.ChangeQueue on Test API Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ChangeQueue</title>
      <link>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/changequeue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/changequeue/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.Render.ChangeQueue
Base class for ChangeQueue.
Generally used by render plugins to build interactive updating of scenes that are being rendered.
public class ChangeQueueProperties Display.DisplayPipelineAttributes DisplayPipelineAttributes  (summary) Get the DisplayPipelineAttributes if available, None otherwise (since) 6.0  bool IsPreview   (summary) Return True if this ChangeQueue is created for preview rendering.
No view was set for preview rendering.
  (since) 6.0
  Guid ViewId   (summary) Return view ID for a RhinoDoc based ChangeQueue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ClippingPlane</title>
      <link>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/clippingplane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/clippingplane/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.Render.ChangeQueue
ChangeQueue clipping plane
public class ClippingPlaneProperties ObjectAttributes Attributes  (summary) Get the ClippingPlaneObject for this clipping plane (since) 6.0  Guid Id  (summary) Get Guid for this clipping plane (since) 6.0  bool IsEnabled  (summary) True if clipping plane is enabled (since) 6.0  Plane Plane  (summary) Get the plane that represents this clipping plane (since) 6.0  ListViewIds  (summary) Get list of View IDs this clipping plane is supposed to clip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DisplayRenderSettings</title>
      <link>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/displayrendersettings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/displayrendersettings/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.Render.ChangeQueue
ChangeQueue DisplayRenderSettings
public class DisplayRenderSettingsProperties bool CullBackFaces  (summary) True if backfaces should be culled (since) 6.0  bool ForceFlatShading  (summary) True if flat shading is forced (since) 6.0  bool SceneLightingOn  (summary) True if scene lighting is enabled (since) 6.0  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DynamicObjectTransform</title>
      <link>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/dynamicobjecttransform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/dynamicobjecttransform/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.Render.ChangeQueue
ChangeQueue DynamicObject
public class DynamicObjectTransformProperties uint MeshInstanceId  (summary) Get the mesh instance id for this dynamic object. (since) 6.0  Transform Transform  (summary) Transform for the DynamicObject (since) 6.0  Methods string ToString()  (summary) String representation of DynamicObject (since) (unknown) (returns) string This is some return comment  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GroundPlane</title>
      <link>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/groundplane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/groundplane/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.Render.ChangeQueue
ChangeQueue ground plane
public class GroundPlaneProperties double Altitude  (summary) Get the altitude for ground plane (since) 6.0  uint Crc  (summary) Get the checksum of this groundplane object (since) 6.0  bool Enabled  (summary) Return True if ground plane is enabled (since) 6.0  bool IsShadowOnly  (summary) Get True if ground plane should be shadow-only (since) 6.0  uint MaterialId  (summary) The CRC / RenderHash of the material on this ground plane (since) 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Light</title>
      <link>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/light/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/light/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.Render.ChangeQueue
ChangeQueue Light change representation
public class LightProperties Event ChangeType  (summary) Get what type of light change this represents (since) 6.0  Geometry.Light Data  (summary) Get the actual light data (since) 6.0  Guid Id  (summary) Get the light object id (since) 6.0  uint IdCrc  (summary) Get CRC computed from Id (since) 6.0  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MappingChannel</title>
      <link>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/mappingchannel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/mappingchannel/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.Render.ChangeQueue
Mapping Channel for a ChangeQueue Mesh
public class MappingChannelProperties Transform Local  (summary) Local transform for the mapping (since) 6.0  TextureMapping Mapping  (summary) Return TexturMapping for this MappingChannel (since) 6.0  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MappingChannelCollection</title>
      <link>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/mappingchannelcollection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/mappingchannelcollection/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.Render.ChangeQueue
MappingChannels for a Mesh
public class MappingChannelCollectionProperties IEnumerableChannels  (summary) Enumerate all available channels in this mapping (since) 6.0  int Count  (summary) Get count of MappingChannels in this collection (since) 6.0  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Material</title>
      <link>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/material/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/material/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.Render.ChangeQueue
Representation of a Material through the change queue
public class MaterialProperties uint Id  (summary) Get the material ID (crc) (since) 6.0  int MeshIndex  (summary) Get mesh index (since) 6.0  uint MeshInstanceId  (summary) Get the material InstanceAncestry (since) 6.0  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mesh</title>
      <link>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/mesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/mesh/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.Render.ChangeQueue
Representation of ChangeQueue Mesh
public class MeshProperties ObjectAttributes Attributes  (summary) Get object attributes of object associated to this mesh. This will be possible only after returning True from ChangeQueue.ProvideOriginalObject() (since) 6.0  MappingChannelCollection Mapping  (summary) Get the mapping for this mesh. (since) 6.0  RhinoObject Object   (summary) Get a copy of the original RhinoObject this Mesh is created from. Possible only after return True from ChangeQueue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MeshInstance</title>
      <link>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/meshinstance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/meshinstance/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.Render.ChangeQueue
Representation of ChangeQueue MeshInstance
public class MeshInstanceProperties bool CastShadows  (summary) Return True if mesh instance should cast shadows (since) 6.0  uint GroupId  (summary) Get identifier that specifies the grouping of these mesh instances - usually based on the object that this originally comprised. (since) 6.0  uint InstanceId  (summary) Get the instance identifier for this mesh instance. (since) 6.0  uint MaterialId  (summary) The Material CRC / RenderHash (since) 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skylight</title>
      <link>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/skylight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/rhino/render/changequeue/skylight/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.Render.ChangeQueue
ChangeQueue skylight
public class SkylightProperties bool Enabled  (summary) Return True if skylight is enabled (since) 6.0  double ShadowIntensity  (summary) Get shadow intensity for skylight (since) 6.0  bool UsesCustomEnvironment  (summary) Return True if skylight uses custom environment (since) 6.0  Methods string ToString()  (summary) Textual representation of Skylight (since) (unknown) (returns) string This is some return comment  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>