<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rhino.FileIO on Test API Site</title>
    <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rhino.FileIO on Test API Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BinaryArchiveException</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/binaryarchiveexception/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/binaryarchiveexception/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Thrown by BinaryArchiveReader and BinaryArchiveWriter classes when an IO error has occured.
public class BinaryArchiveExceptionConstructors BinaryArchiveException(string message)  (summary) Initializes a new instance of the class. (since) 5.0  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BinaryArchiveFile</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/binaryarchivefile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/binaryarchivefile/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
public class BinaryArchiveFileConstructors BinaryArchiveFile(string filename,BinaryArchiveMode mode)  (summary) (since) 5.1  Properties BinaryArchiveReader Reader  (summary) (since) 5.1  BinaryArchiveWriter Writer  (summary) (since) 5.1  Methods void Close()  (summary) (since) 5.1 (returns) void This is some return comment  void Dispose()  (summary) Actively reclaims unmanaged resources that this instance uses. (since) 5.1 (returns) void This is some return comment  bool Open()  (summary) (since) 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BinaryArchiveReader</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/binaryarchivereader/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/binaryarchivereader/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Represents an entity that is capable of reading a binary archive and instantiating strongly-typed objects.
public class BinaryArchiveReaderProperties int Archive3dmVersion  (summary) If a 3dm archive is being read or written, then this is the version of the 3dm archive format (1, 2, 3, 4 or 5). 0 a 3dm archive is not being read/written 1 a version 1 3dm archive is being read/written 2 a version 2 3dm archive is being read/written 3 a version 3 3dm archive is being read/written 4 a version 4 3dm archive is being read/written 5 an old version 5 3dm archive is being read 50 a version 5 3dm archive is being read/written.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BinaryArchiveWriter</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/binaryarchivewriter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/binaryarchivewriter/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Represents an entity that is able to write data to an archive.
public class BinaryArchiveWriterProperties int Archive3dmVersion  (summary) If a 3dm archive is being read or written, then this is the version of the 3dm archive format (1, 2, 3, 4 or 5). 0 a 3dm archive is not being read/written 1 a version 1 3dm archive is being read/written 2 a version 2 3dm archive is being read/written 3 a version 3 3dm archive is being read/written 4 a version 4 3dm archive is being read/written 5 an old version 5 3dm archive is being read 50 a version 5 3dm archive is being read/written.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CommonComponentTable</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/commoncomponenttable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/commoncomponenttable/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Provides a base table type that encompasses all document tables, both in RhinoDoc and File3dm.
public class CommonComponentTableProperties ModelComponentType ComponentType  (summary) Returns the actual component type of a table. (since) (unknown)  int Count  (summary) Returns the count of all items, including deleted ones. (since) (unknown)  Methods void Clear()  (summary) Marks all items as deleted. (since) (unknown) (returns) void This is some return comment  bool Delete(T item)  (summary) Deletes an item.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ContentHash</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/contenthash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/contenthash/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Contains information that is useful to uniquly identify an object. This object is immutable.
public class ContentHashstatic !=  (summary) Determines if two ContentHash instances are different by value. (since) 6.0  static ==  (summary) Determines if two ContentHash instances are equal by value. (since) 6.0  Properties ulong ByteCount  (summary) Gets the length of the content, in bytes. (since) 6.0  DateTime HashTime  (summary) Gets the hash time, rounded to seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DracoCompression</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/dracocompression/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/dracocompression/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Google draco compression for mesh and point cloud data
public class DracoCompressionMethods static DracoCompression Compress(Mesh mesh)  (summary) Compress a mesh using default compression options. (since) 7.0 (returns) DracoCompression This is some return comment  static DracoCompression Compress(Mesh mesh,DracoCompressionOptions options)  (summary) Compress a mesh (since) 7.0 (returns) DracoCompression This is some return comment  static Rhino.Geometry.GeometryBase DecompressBase64String(string encoded)  (summary) Decompress base64 encoded version of draco data into either a mesh or point cloud (since) 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DracoCompressionOptions</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/dracocompressionoptions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/dracocompressionoptions/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Options for applying drac compression
public class DracoCompressionOptionsConstructors DracoCompressionOptions()  (summary) Initializes to default options (since) 7.0  Properties int CompressionLevel  (summary) Compression level. 0 if fastest, but least compression. 10 is slowest, but best compression (since) 7.0  int NormalQuantizationBits  (summary) Sets the quantization compression options for normal values. The values will be quantized in a box defined by the maximum extent of the values.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File3dm</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dm/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Represents a 3dm file, which is stored using the OpenNURBS file standard. The 3dm format is the main Rhinoceros storage format.Visit http://www.opennurbs.com/ for more details.
public class File3dmConstructors File3dm()  (summary) Initializes a new instance of a 3dm file. (since) 5.0  Properties File3dmDimStyleTable AllDimStyles  (summary) Dimension Styles in this file. (since) 6.0  File3dmGroupTable AllGroups  (summary) Grpups in this file. (since) 6.5  File3dmHatchPatternTable AllHatchPatterns  (summary) Hatch patterns in this file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File3dmCommonComponentTable</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmcommoncomponenttable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmcommoncomponenttable/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Provides a base table type that is shared among all File3dm tables.
public class File3dmCommonComponentTableMethods void Add(T item)  (summary) Adds an item. (since) (unknown) (returns) void This is some return comment  void Delete(int index)  (summary) Flags a component as deleted. (since) (unknown) (returns) void This is some return comment  bool Delete(T item)  (summary) Flags a component as deleted. (since) (unknown) (returns) bool This is some return comment  string Dump()  (summary) Prepares a text dump of object table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File3dmDimStyleTable</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmdimstyletable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmdimstyletable/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Provides access to annotation styles in the 3dm file.
public class File3dmDimStyleTableProperties ModelComponentType ComponentType  (summary) Returns . (since) 6.0  Methods DimensionStyle FindIndex(int index)  (summary) Retrieves a DimensionStyle object based on Index. This search type of search is discouraged. We are moving towards using only IDs for all tables. (since) 6.0 (returns) DimensionStyle This is some return comment  DimensionStyle FindName(string name)  (summary) Finds a DimensionStyle given its name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File3dmGroupTable</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmgrouptable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmgrouptable/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Provides access to groups in the 3dm file.
public class File3dmGroupTableProperties ModelComponentType ComponentType  (summary) Returns . (since) 6.5  Methods Group FindIndex(int groupIndex)  (summary) Retrieves a Group object based on an index. This search type of search is discouraged. We are moving towards using only IDs for all tables. (since) 6.5 (returns) Group This is some return comment  Group FindName(string name)  (summary) Finds a Group given its name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File3dmHatchPatternTable</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmhatchpatterntable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmhatchpatterntable/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Provides access to hatch pattern definitions in the 3dm file.
public class File3dmHatchPatternTableProperties ModelComponentType ComponentType  (summary) Returns . (since) 6.0  Methods HatchPattern FindIndex(int index)  (summary) Retrieves a HatchPattern object based on Index. This search type of search is discouraged. We are moving towards using only IDs for all tables. (since) 6.0 (returns) HatchPattern This is some return comment  HatchPattern FindName(string name)  (summary) Finds a HatchPattern given its name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File3dmInstanceDefinitionTable</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dminstancedefinitiontable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dminstancedefinitiontable/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Provides access to instance (block) definitions in the 3dm file.
public class File3dmInstanceDefinitionTableProperties ModelComponentType ComponentType  (summary) Returns . (since) 6.0  Methods int Add(string name,string description,Point3d basePoint,GeometryBase geometry,ObjectAttributes attributes)  (summary) Adds an instance definition to the instance definition table. (since) 6.5 (returns) int This is some return comment  int Add(string name,string description,Point3d basePoint,IEnumerablegeometry)  (summary) Adds an instance definition to the instance definition table. (since) 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File3dmLayerTable</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmlayertable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmlayertable/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Provides access to layers in the 3dm file.
public class File3dmLayerTableProperties ModelComponentType ComponentType  (summary) Returns . (since) 6.0  Methods Layer FindIndex(int index)  (summary) Retrieves a Layer object based on Index. This search type of search is discouraged. We are moving towards using only IDs for all tables. (since) 6.0 (returns) Layer This is some return comment  Layer FindName(string name,Guid parentId)  (summary) Finds a Layer given its name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File3dmLinetypeTable</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmlinetypetable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmlinetypetable/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Provides access to Linetypes in the 3dm file.
public class File3dmLinetypeTableProperties ModelComponentType ComponentType  (summary) Returns . (since) 6.0  Methods Linetype FindIndex(int index)  (summary) Retrieves a Linetype object based on Index. This search type of search is discouraged. We are moving towards using only IDs for all tables. (since) 6.0 (returns) Linetype This is some return comment  Linetype FindName(string name)  (summary) Finds a Linetype given its name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File3dmMaterialTable</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmmaterialtable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmmaterialtable/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Provides access to materials in the 3dm file.
public class File3dmMaterialTableProperties ModelComponentType ComponentType  (summary) Returns . (since) 6.0  Methods DocObjects.Material FindIndex(int index)  (summary) Retrieves a material based on Index. This search type of search is discouraged. We are moving towards using only IDs for all tables. (since) 6.0 (returns) DocObjects.Material This is some return comment  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File3dmNamedConstructionPlanes</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmnamedconstructionplanes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmnamedconstructionplanes/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Provides access to namned construction planes in the 3dm file.
public class File3dmNamedConstructionPlanesProperties int Count  (summary) Number of named construction planes in the table. (since) 6.0  Methods void Add(ConstructionPlane cplane)  (summary) Adds a named construction plane to the table. (since) 6.0 (returns) void This is some return comment  int Add(string name,Plane plane)  (summary) Adds a named construction plane to the table. (since) 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File3dmNotes</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmnotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmnotes/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Represents the notes information stored in a 3dm file.
public class File3dmNotesConstructors File3dmNotes()  (summary) Creates empty default notes (since) 5.0  Properties bool IsHtml  (summary) Gets or sets the text format. If the format is HTML, true; False otherwise. (since) 5.0  bool IsVisible  (summary) Gets or sets the notes visibility. If the notes are visible, true; False otherwise. (since) 5.0  string Notes  (summary) Gets or sets the text content of the notes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File3dmObject</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmobject/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmobject/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Used to store geometry table object definition and attributes in a File3dm.
public class File3dmObjectProperties ObjectAttributes Attributes  (summary) Gets the attributes that are linked with this document object. (since) 5.0  ModelComponentType ComponentType  (summary) Returns . (since) 6.0  GeometryBase Geometry  (summary) Gets the geometry that is linked with this document object. (since) 5.0  string Name  (summary) Gets or sets the Name of the object.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File3dmObjectTable</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmobjecttable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmobjecttable/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Represents a simple object table for a file that is open externally. This class mimics Rhino.DocObjects.Tables.ObjectTable while providing external eccess to the file.
public class File3dmObjectTableProperties ModelComponentType ComponentType  (summary) Returns . (since) 6.0  int Count  (summary) Returns the total amount of items in the object table, including lights. (since) 5.0  Methods void Add(File3dmObject item)  (summary) Duplicates the object, then adds a copy of the object to the document.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File3dmPlugInData</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmplugindata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmplugindata/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Custom data in the file supplied by a plug-in
public class File3dmPlugInDataProperties Guid PlugInId  (summary) Plug-in this data is associated with (since) 5.0  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File3dmPlugInDataTable</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmplugindatatable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmplugindatatable/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Table of custom data provided by plug-ins
public class File3dmPlugInDataTableProperties int Count  (summary) Gets the number of File3dmPlugInData in this table. (since) 5.0  Methods void Clear()  (summary) Remove all entries from this table (since) 5.0 (returns) void This is some return comment  string Dump()  (summary) Prepares a text dump of table. (since) 5.0 (returns) string This is some return comment  IEnumeratorGetEnumerator()  (summary) Gets the enumerator that visits any in this table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File3dmSettings</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmsettings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmsettings/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
General settings in a 3dm file.
public class File3dmSettingsProperties double ModelAbsoluteTolerance  (summary) Gets or sets the model space absolute tolerance. (since) 5.0  double ModelAngleToleranceDegrees  (summary) Gets or sets the model space angle tolerance. (since) 5.0  double ModelAngleToleranceRadians  (summary) Gets or sets the model space angle tolerance. (since) 5.0  Point3d ModelBasepoint  (summary) Gets or sets the model basepoint that is used when the file is read as an instance definition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File3dmStringTable</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmstringtable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmstringtable/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Provides access to document strings in the 3dm file.
public class File3dmStringTableProperties int Count  (summary) Returns the number of document strings in the 3dm file. (since) 6.0  int DocumentUserTextCount  (summary) Returns the number of Section/Entry-style key values. (since) 6.0  Methods void Delete(string key)  (summary) Removes a document string from the 3dm file. (since) 6.0 (returns) void This is some return comment  void Delete(string section,string entry)  (summary) Removes document strings from the 3dm file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File3dmViewTable</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmviewtable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmviewtable/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Provides access to views in the 3dm file.
public class File3dmViewTableProperties int Count  (summary) Gets the amount of items in the table. (since) 6.0  Methods void Add(ViewInfo item)  (summary) Adds a (since) 6.0 (returns) void This is some return comment  void Clear()  (summary) Removes all items from the table. (since) 6.0 (returns) void This is some return comment  bool Contains(ViewInfo item)  (summary) Returns an indication of the presence of a view in the table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File3dmWriteOptions</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmwriteoptions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/file3dmwriteoptions/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Options used by File3dm.Write
public class File3dmWriteOptionsConstructors File3dmWriteOptions()  (summary) Initializes properties to defaults. (since) 5.9  Properties bool SaveAnalysisMeshes  (summary) Include analysis meshes in the file. Default is true (since) 5.9  bool SaveRenderMeshes  (summary) Include Render meshes in the file. Default is true (since) 5.9  bool SaveUserData  (summary) Include custom user data in the file. Default is true (since) 5.9  int Version  (summary) File version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FileObj</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/fileobj/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/fileobj/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Support for obj file format
public class FileObjMethods static bool Read(String filename,RhinoDoc doc,FileObjReadOptions options)  (summary) (since) 6.0 (returns) bool This is some return comment  static WriteFileResult Write(StreamWriter stream,RhinoDoc doc,FileObjWriteOptions options)  (summary) Write an obj stream based on the contents of a RhinoDoc (since) 7.0 (returns) WriteFileResult This is some return comment  static WriteFileResult Write(String filename,Mesh[] meshes,FileObjWriteOptions options)  (summary) Write an obj file with an array of meshes (since) 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FileObjReadOptions</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/fileobjreadoptions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/fileobjreadoptions/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Options used when reading an obj file.
public class FileObjReadOptionsConstructors FileObjReadOptions(FileReadOptions readOptions)  (summary) (since) 6.0  Properties bool DisplayColorFromObjMaterial  (summary) Determines whether textures are read from the .mtl file, if it exists. (since) 6.5  bool IgnoreTextures  (summary) Determines whether textures are read from the .mtl file, if it exists. (since) 6.0  bool MapYtoZ  (summary) Setting to transform OBJ&amp;rsquo;s Y axis to Rhino&amp;rsquo;s Z axis (since) 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FileObjWriteOptions</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/fileobjwriteoptions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/fileobjwriteoptions/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
public class FileObjWriteOptionsConstructors FileObjWriteOptions(FileWriteOptions writeOptions)  (summary) (since) 6.0  Properties string ActualFilePathOnMac  (summary) (since) 6.3  bool CreateNgons  (summary) Setting to enable/diable the creation of ngons for the output (since) 6.0  bool CullUnnecessaryVertexesInNgons  (summary) Setting to determine whether interior colinear vertexes are part of the ngon. (since) 6.0  AsciiEol EolType  (summary) (since) 6.0  ObjGroupNames ExportGroupNameLayerNames  (summary) Setting to determine whether object, group or layer names will become &amp;ldquo;g&amp;quot;s in the OBJ output file (since) 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FilePdf</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/filepdf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/filepdf/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Support for PDF file format
public class FilePdfstatic PreWrite  (summary) Fired immediately before a Pdf is written (since) 6.0  Methods static FilePdf Create()  (summary) Create a new instance of a FilePdf class (since) 6.0 (returns) FilePdf This is some return comment  int AddPage(int widthInDots,int heightInDots,int dotsPerInch)  (summary) Add a blank page to this document (since) 6.5 (returns) int This is some return comment  int AddPage(ViewCaptureSettings settings)  (summary) Add a new page to this document and draw a viewport into it based on provided ViewCaptureSettings (since) 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FilePdfEventArgs</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/filepdfeventargs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/filepdfeventargs/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Used for events that are fired while constructing/saving a Pdf
public class FilePdfEventArgsProperties FilePdf Pdf  (summary) The document that is about to be written (since) 6.0  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FilePly</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/fileply/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/fileply/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Support for ply file format
public class FilePlyMethods static WriteFileResult Write(String filename,RhinoDoc doc,FilePlyWriteOptions options)  (summary) Write a ply file based on the contents of a RhinoDoc (since) 7.0 (returns) WriteFileResult This is some return comment  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FilePlyWriteOptions</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/fileplywriteoptions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/fileplywriteoptions/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
public class FilePlyWriteOptionsConstructors FilePlyWriteOptions(FileWriteOptions writeOptions)  (summary) (since) 7.0  Properties bool ExportASCII  (summary) Determines whether to export as Ascii. (since) 7.0  bool ExportColors  (summary) Determines whether to export vertex colors. (since) 7.0  bool ExportMaterial  (summary) Determines whether to export a material. (since) 7.0  bool ExportNormals  (summary) Determines whether to export vertex normals. (since) 7.0  MeshingParameters MeshingParameters  (summary) (since) 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FileReadOptions</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/filereadoptions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/filereadoptions/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
public class FileReadOptionsConstructors FileReadOptions()  (summary) (since) 5.0  Properties bool BatchMode  (summary) True means you cannot ask questions during reading. (no dialogs, no &amp;ldquo;getters&amp;rdquo;, etc.) (since) 5.0  bool ImportMode   (summary) True means we are merging whatever is being read into an existing document. This means you need to consider things like:
If the information being read is in a different unit system, it should be scaled if UseScaleGeometry is true.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FileReference</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/filereference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/filereference/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Manages a reference to an existing or nonexisting file, using either or both absolute or relative paths. Once constructed, this class is immutable.
public class FileReferenceConstructors FileReference(string fullPath,string relativePath,ContentHash hash,FileReferenceStatus status)  (summary) Constructs a new instance of the FileReference class, given a fullPath, a relativePath a content hash and a status value. (since) 6.0  Properties ContentHash ContentHash  (summary) Gets the content hash. (since) 6.0  string FullPath  (summary) Gets the absolute path of this file reference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FileSlc</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/fileslc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/fileslc/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Support for writing slice (slc) file format
public class FileSlcMethods static bool Write(string filename,RhinoDoc doc,FileSlcWriteOptions options)  (summary) Write a slc file based on the contents of a RhinoDoc (since) 7.0 (returns) bool This is some return comment  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FileSlcWriteOptions</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/fileslcwriteoptions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/fileslcwriteoptions/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Options used when writing a slc file
public class FileSlcWriteOptionsProperties double AngleBetweenSegmentsDegrees  (summary) The angle that determines how smooth the polylines of the slice curves will be. When the number is small you will get a smooth final output but it will take more time to export and a larger file. (since) 7.0  Point3d EndPoint  (summary) End of the slicing normal (since) 7.0  double SliceDistance  (summary) The distance between the slices or layers of curves that your final output will contain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FileStp</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/filestp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/filestp/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Support for writing step (stp) file format
public class FileStpMethods static bool Write(string filename,RhinoDoc doc,FileStpWriteOptions options)  (summary) Write a stp file based on the contents of a RhinoDoc (since) 7.0 (returns) bool This is some return comment  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FileStpWriteOptions</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/filestpwriteoptions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/filestpwriteoptions/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Options used when writing a stp file
public class FileStpWriteOptionsProperties bool Export2dCurves  (summary) Some (not most, and not Rhino) importing applications can make use of the 2-D trimming curves to get a more accurate and faster import. The size of the step file will be larger (since) 7.0  bool ExportBlack  (summary) Let importing application set color for black objects. If a Rhino object has color black, no color is assigned to the object in the step file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FileType</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/filetype/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/filetype/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
public class FileTypeConstructors FileType(string extension,string description)  (summary) (since) 5.0  Properties string Description  (summary) (since) 5.0  string Extension  (summary) (since) 5.0  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FileWriteOptions</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/filewriteoptions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/filewriteoptions/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
public class FileWriteOptionsConstructors FileWriteOptions()  (summary) (since) 5.0  Properties string DestinationFileName  (summary) For use on Apple frameworks only. Retrns the final destination file name. (since) 6.3  int FileVersion  (summary) (since) 5.0  bool IncludeBitmapTable  (summary) The file written should include the bitmap table if your File Writing Plug-in supports it. (since) 5.0  bool IncludeHistory  (summary) The file written should include history information if your File Writing Plug-In supports it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ImageFile</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/imagefile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/imagefile/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Support functions for image files
public class ImageFileMethods static bool SupportsAlphaChannel(string filename)  (summary) Returns True if file at given path is an image file and that file format supports an alpha channel (since) 6.0 (returns) bool This is some return comment  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ManifestTable</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/manifesttable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/manifesttable/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Maintains an index to every model component that is in the 3dm file. This is the &amp;ldquo;more comprehensive&amp;rdquo; table that contains all objects in all other tables.
public class ManifestTableProperties ModelComponentType ComponentType  (summary) Returns . (since) 6.0  int Count  (summary) Total number of items in the manifest, including deleted items. (since) 6.0  long LongCount  (summary) Total number of items in the manifest, including deleted items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NameHash</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/namehash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/namehash/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Contains information that is useful to uniquly identify an object name. This object is immutable.
public class NameHashstatic !=  (summary) Determines if two NameHash instances are different by value. (since) 6.0  static ==  (summary) Determines if two NameHash instances are equal by value. (since) 6.0  Constructors NameHash(string name)  (summary) Creates a new NameHash, representing a piece of text. (since) 6.0  NameHash(string name,Guid parentId)  (summary) Creates a new NameHash, representing a piece of text.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SerializationOptions</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/serializationoptions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/serializationoptions/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Contains options for serializing -or storing- data, such as Rhino version and user data.
public class SerializationOptionsConstructors SerializationOptions()  (summary) Initializes a new instance of the class. (since) 5.0  Properties int RhinoVersion  (summary) Gets or sets a value indicating the Rhino version. (since) 5.0  bool WriteUserData  (summary) Gets or sets a value indicating whether to write user data. (since) 5.0  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHA1OpenNURBS</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/sha1opennurbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/sha1opennurbs/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Provides the OpenNURBS implementation of SHA1.
This class is provided only with the purpose of hashing. It is not meant to be used for any cryptographic purpose.
public class SHA1OpenNURBSConstructors SHA1OpenNURBS()  (summary) Constructs a new instance of the SHA1 algorithm. (since) 6.0  Methods static byte[] FileSystemPathHash(string path,bool? ignoreCase)  (summary) Computes the SHA1 hash of a file system path, converted to UTF8. These file system paths have identical values of FileSystemPathHash():/x/y/z/name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TextLog</title>
      <link>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/textlog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hugo/posts/rhino/fileio/textlog/</guid>
      <description>Namespace: Rhino.FileIO
Used for collecting text data
public class TextLogConstructors TextLog()  (summary) Creates a text log that stores all text in memory. Use ToString on this version of the TextLog to get the text that we written (since) 5.1  TextLog(IntPtr ptr)  (summary) (since) 6.0  TextLog(string filename)  (summary) Creates a text log that writes all text to a file. If no filename is provided, then text is written to StdOut (since) 5.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>